This is my workstation setup in 2026 in
Tokyo. Since my last workstation video,
a lot has changed. I've moved to Japan.
I've imported some of my favorite
things, and I've set up a completely new
workstation. In many ways, I think this
is one of my favorite setups of all
time. I feel extremely productive and
locked in at this desk. During the
daytime, I set up my iPod setup, my
journal setup, and it's the perfect
place to get everything I need done in a
day. And in the night time, it's also a
really nice place to relax, to watch a
movie, just chill out, and there's a
cool vibe. So, I want to show you
everything in detail. And at the end,
I'm also going to show you one of the
coolest things that I've set up since my
last video, which is my own home server.
But before we start the video, I just
want to say I really appreciate you guys
watching and subscribing to the channel.
When I looked at the analytics, only 60%
of you guys who watch my channel
regularly are subscribed. So, if you
could help me out by subscribing, I'll
make sure to continue providing value
and continue to make better videos. But
yeah, let's get into the video. So, the
first thing is I got a new desk. Because
I moved to a new country, I couldn't
bring my old desk. And when I looked
into it, there's actually a really cool
brand in Japan called Predux that makes
highly customizable sitting and standing
desk. So, as you would expect, there's a
button that you can use to easily change
the height level of your desk. But one
upgrade from my previous standing desk
is that there is a preset standing and
sitting position. So I can go between
sitting and standing with just one
click. The actual standing desk
mechanism is made by this company called
Flexispot. But what this Japanese
company Predux does is that they make
their own custom tabletop. So with their
tabletop, they make it so that you can
mount a bunch of things underneath the
desk. And the first most useful thing I
mounted under the desk is this drawer.
So in here I put pens, guitar picks, USB
drives, and chargers. just the stuff
that I need to access really quickly on
my desk. And the second thing I mounted
is my audio interface underneath the
desk. The cool thing about their desk is
that you can mount stuff underneath
without having to use any screws. And
it's also really modular to move things
around underneath the desk. The third
thing I've mounted underneath the desk
is cable organization. So, this company
has really solved the issue of having a
bunch of cables underneath your desk. If
you want to hide your cables away, it
makes it really difficult to make any
modifications later. And if you don't
hide your cables underneath your desk,
then you just have a bunch of cables
that you might pull on if you just kick
on it. So with their setup, they have
this net that captures everything and
yet you can still easily access them and
make any changes. So within those wires,
I also mounted a charging cable made by
Native Union. And what's unique about
this cable is that it has two heads. So
you can either charge USBC or lightning
with the same head. This really comes in
handy because I still have some devices
that still use lightning like my AirPods
Max and also my iPod Nano. To easily
access the cable underneath the desk, I
use this mount made by this company
called Elevation Lab. And there's a
little clip on it that holds the cable
in place. So when I'm not using it, it
just disappears and when I need it, I
can easily pull it out with one hand.
But before I talk about the stuff that's
on top of the desk, I also want to talk
about the chair that I use. So, I ended
up getting the same chair that I used in
my old workstation and it's totally
worth it. This is the Herman Miller
Embody Logitech collab, which if you've
only tried the Logitech Embody before,
it is a complete different experience
and a massive improvement. It's
definitely on the pricier side, but for
me personally, I think it's totally
worth it to upgrade the places that you
spend the most time at, which for me is
my workstation and my bed. But once you
use a chair like this, it's really hard
to go back to just a cheap office chair
or some IKEA chair, which really get
quite uncomfortable if you sit for long
periods of time and can cause a lot of
issues later down the line. And probably
one of the most uncomfortable things to
sit with is bad finances. And that's
where the sponsor of this video comes
in, Copilot Money. So Copilot Money is a
super simple to use finance and budget
app that makes it easy to track your
spending, your income, your investments,
and even your subscriptions. As someone
who's been using Copile Money for two
years now before they sponsored any of
my videos, let me show you what makes it
stand out. First, as someone who is
self-employed and makes money through
many different sources, there really is
no better app to stay on top of my
finances. It's helped me spend
responsibly and even plan for big
purchases. Not only can I track my
income so I never spend more than I
make, but I can also keep track of all
my subscriptions in one tab right here.
Through this, I've actually caught
multiple times different companies
trying to charge me even though I
canceled. And so it saved me a ton of
money. And with investing, this is also
the best app by far to keep track of all
of my investments. I can easily track my
cost basis, my performance over time,
and even compare it to an index or ETF.
It connects to all my accounts
automatically, so I can easily track my
net worth at one glance. Even for
illquid investments, you can track them
manually. If you feel like you're behind
on your finances or you haven't hit your
net worth goals yet, this is one of the
highest ROI things you can do because
ultimately you can't improve what you
don't measure. And Copilot Money makes
it super easy to track and measure your
finances. I really appreciate the fact
that they have a super transparent and
honest business model and I've easily
recommended to all my family and
friends. So if you want to try it out as
well, you can use my code race 2 for 2
months completely for free or check out
this link right here. It's available on
iOS, iPad OS, Mac OS, and the web. Check
it out. And let's get back into the
video. Moving on to the desk itself. I
did bring my iPad mount, which is
mounted here on the left. And this mount
is just a magnetic mount that lets me
use my iPad as a third monitor for my
computer. It's quite nice to use an iPad
as a third monitor because use touch
inputs. You can use native iPad apps and
it's the perfect size if you want to
play a podcast or have your to-do list
or calendar open to the left of you. And
if you use Sidecar, which is built into
iPad OS, it's really seamless to use it
as a monitor. You can drag Windows over
and there's zero latency. The main
monitor that I use is the Studio
Display, which is still the same
monitor. And I find this to be the
perfect size. I think one of the best
selling points of this monitor is that
it just has everything on one. It has
speakers, webcam, and dock all built
into the monitor. And I think it's
really one of the cleanest design
monitors that you can buy. On top of the
monitor, I use a monitor light called
Screen Bar Halo. And the reason why I
like this monitor light is because at
night, I can turn off all the lights and
just only use the screen light to use my
computer with much less eye strain. So,
it not only lights up the keyboard, but
also lights up the wall behind it for a
nice cool effect when I'm watching a
movie on my desk or something like that.
But moving on to the right, I have my
filming setup. That is the Sony A7S3,
which is what I've been using to film
pretty much all my videos for a while
now. And I also got this little small
studio light made by Elgato Labs, which
I put right here. And right here is a
maxed out MacBook Pro, which basically
powers everything here. The MacBook is
sitting on a laptop stand made by Rain
Design. And I added a small modification
so that I could place my journal here.
I've been journaling for almost 10 years
now. And the way that I like to journal
is with this method called the life
tracker system. It's probably one of the
best ways I found to track and optimize
my life so that I don't forget the
things I'm working on, the things I have
going on in my life, and the things I'm
thinking about. So, having the journal
out and open to the monthly page at my
workstation has been super underrated
and important for me to keep up the
habit of journaling. So, if journaling
is something that you're interested in,
I would highly recommend you get a full
journal and put on your desk so that you
can always see it and remind yourself of
it. Now moving back towards the left
again. One cool thing that I got is this
USB hub that also has this small
monitor. So this is a super cute monitor
that you can connect to your Mac as an
extended screen. It's way too small to
actually do any real work on. So it's
not really for that, but it's really
useful if you want to have something
displayed in the corner. For me, one
thing that I like to use it for is I
like to have my cloud code terminal open
in the small monitor here so that I can
type something and I can see and monitor
the progress without it taking up space
on the main computer. But to the left of
this USB hub, I have an actual Macintosh
clone that is just an alarm clock. So,
doesn't really have any cool features,
but I really like the design of the
Macintosh. And the practical way that I
use this is I set the time and date to
Pacific time in America. So I can always
see what time and date it is when I'm
getting on calls or even just checking
the stock market. Next is a timer that I
use to set Pomodoro timers. And this is
a visual timer made by this company
called Time Timer. This is the one that
I've been using for many years now. But
recently I got this one that is kind of
fun that I just been testing out. This
is a little cube that you can set timers
just by flipping it to different angles.
But honestly, I don't think it really
matters what timer you use. But I find
that using a Pomodoro timer is really
useful for staying on task. If you guys
have a timer of choice, definitely let
me know and I'll be interested in
checking it out. To the left, I have
this little phone stand that I've
mounted to the desk that I can either
put a pocket notebook with some
reminders or to-dos or a phone. So,
right now, I just put my ebook reader,
the books pelma, and sometimes I'll pick
it up and I'll read something on my
desk. But in the back of my desk, I have
this label maker made by this company
called King Gym. So, this is not really
part of the workstation, but it's at my
desk. The reason why I have this label
maker at my desk is because labels can
really help you with organization and
making sure that your workstation or
room doesn't descend into chaos. My
favorite label maker is the one that
you've seen on this channel called the
Daimo Label Maker, which makes these
really nice black labels. But I recently
came across this label maker, which is
basically a professional label maker in
Japan that you can use to label cables,
write extended sentences, or even make
QR codes. So, this has been a massive
upgrade to take my organization to the
next level. But moving on to the center
of the desk is my keyboard. This is my
favorite keyboard, the HHKB Studio. And
I also made a short about this. But the
reason why I really like this keyboard
is first, it's really compact with no
air keys. And second, it has a
trackpoint knob. So this knob right
here, this red dot right here, allows me
to control the mouse without having to
move my fingers anywhere. And so most of
the time, I don't even really need to
use a mouse unless I'm doing something
very specific or technical design work.
And so it's just a lot more ergonomic.
Personally, I like to use the keyboard
in wired mode because it just has the
fastest response time and has no
Bluetooth connectivity issues or battery
issues. The mouse that I use is the
Logitech MX Anywhere. a super compact
mouse. So, if I'm traveling and I'm
using my computer, I also bring this
mouse with me. I found out that it's
actually possible to connect an Apple TV
remote to your Mac and control it. So,
the Apple TV remote is actually
surprisingly extremely natural to use
with a monitor display. It's not
natively supported, but there's an app
that once you install allows you to
control your entire computer with an
Apple TV remote. The dial on the remote
is super sensitive, so it works really
nicely as a mouse to control your
cursor. And there's a mic button that
you can click to give commands, to
control your windows, to open different
apps, or even to dictate messages. So,
sometimes I like to just kick my feet up
at my desk and just use the remote to do
all the things I need to do. Especially
if I'm doing something like cloud code
or some agentic AI stuff. It's actually
quite fun. And obviously if I'm just
watching a movie at my desk or
something, you can pause, play, adjust
the volume, mute. And using this really
makes me think maybe in the future we
won't even really need a keyboard and
mouse to use our computers. Like maybe
we can just have a remote and talk to an
AI and it can pretty much do everything.
Yeah, if you have an Apple TV remote
that you're not using, I'd recommend you
to check out this app. It's called Go to
Remote and it just makes it super fun to
use your computer. Underneath the desk
mouse, I have this cutting board desk
mat. And this cutting board desk mat has
a plastic film on top. So it lets me put
reminders or photos underneath and it's
sort of like a constant reminder that I
can see all throughout the day. So for
example, if I have bills I need to pay,
I'll put it underneath here. Or some
pictures or reminders, I'll put it
underneath here next to my keyboard. If
you want this specific one, it's a
little bit niche. I personally just got
it at some random stationary store, so
there may be better ones, but I'll link
this one if you're interested in getting
this exact one. To the right of my desk,
I have a little shelf, which I mainly
use to put my amp. This is a practice
amp that I have connected to my guitar,
so I can easily just pick up my guitar
and practice at any time. But it's also
connected to my iPod Nano, so I can use
my iPod Nano to play music on my desk. I
have lowfi beats, brown noise, white
noise, and some of my favorite playlists
on my iPod. And it's really nice that
it's just completely disconnected from
my computer and runs independently.
Besides this amp, I also just have a
bunch of miscellaneous stuff mounted on
the walls like my headphones, scissors,
tape, remote control, and my glasses.
And it's really useful to be able to
organize and access these things at arms
length. But the last thing I want to
show you guys, which is what I mentioned
in the beginning of my video, is one of
my coolest upgrades to my workstation,
and it's my home lab. So, this area is
basically just a regular closet that I
have for books and also different
drawers. But this section right here is
basically my home lab, which is my home
server. So, I talked about this in my
home server setup video. Rather than
paying for cloud subscriptions or
different media subscriptions, I now
prefer to just own everything and to
sync them with my own devices locally.
So, even with a password manager, I no
longer pay a subscription to host my
passwords in some random server.
Instead, I host them in my own server
that I can access through all my
devices. And it's actually far more
secure with the exact same workflow. So,
I also do something similar with my
files and my photos. And in this
computer right here, I have 75
terabytes. So, it's pretty much more
storage than I'll ever need. And it's
nice that it's just a onetime cost
versus a subscription fee. But if you're
interested, you can check out that video
that I made. Besides the server, there's
also this MacBook Air setup, which is
just a MacBook running OpenClaw. If you
don't know what OpenClaw is, it's an AI
setup that you can install on any
computer that makes it so that you have
an AI that is controlling and taking
over your entire computer. And the way
that you talk through the AI is through
a messaging app like WhatsApp, Signal,
Telegram, anything of your choice. And
then you can just tell the AI to do
anything on that computer. So it could
book reservations for you, it can write
emails for you, it can do research for
you. and I can just look over and see
this AI working while I'm also working
at my desk. If you enjoy this video, you
can check out the previous video that I
made about my workstation, or you can
check out this video, which is about my
top five buy for life items. And I'll
see you over there. Let's get it.